Guide to the Ervin S. Hubbard glass plate negative collection, 1895-1901 MS2381
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Geographic locations, 1893-1901; Series 1
  - Maryland, Virginia, and Washington D.C., Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1895 August 28; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 20)
      Washington's tomb: front view
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1898 August 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 21)
      Washington's tomb: general view
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1898 August 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 22)
      Washington's tomb: interior
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1895 August 28; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 23)
      Washington's tomb: side view
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1895 August 28; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 24)
      West front of mansion
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1895 August 28; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 25)
      West front of mansion; "Imperial" plate
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 1)
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 2)
    - National Museum Grounds, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 26)
      California tree
    - National Museum, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 3)
      A & I Building
    - National Museum, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 27)
    - "The National Tribune" Offices, 1894 March 1; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 28)
      N.Y. Ave. near 17th St.; Washington, DC; 24-3; Lemon Building
    - Nottingham, Maryland, 1898 July 28; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 29)
      On Patuxent River; "Near this place the Bristish landed part of their forces in 1812 and marched across the country to Bladensburg."
    - "Octagon House", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 3, Box 10, Item 30)
      Tayloe Mansion; 18th St. N.Y. Ave.; Washington, DC
    - Octagon House, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 1)
      No. 2
    - The Old Willard, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 2)
      14th and Penn. Ave.
    - "Palais Royal", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 3)
      A. Lisner, Prop.; Cor. 11th and G St.; Washington, DC; 24-1
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 4)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 5)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 6)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 7)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 8)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 9)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 10)
    - Parade, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 11)
    - Pennsylvannia Avenue, 1895 March 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 12)
      From Capitol Terrace; Washington, DC
    - Prescott Home, Washington DC, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 4)
      at home, 716 20th St. NW; Washington, DC; Mother - Sarah Prescott Hubbard; Son - Laurence Hubbard; Daughter - Helen Hubbard (later Lawton)
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 14; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 13)
      Residence of Mr. Clover; No. 1535 N.H. Ave.; Washington, DC; 10-1; Newspaper
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 14; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 14)
      Residence; No. 1535-33 N.H. Ave.; Washington, DC; 10-2
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 15)
      Residence; 1721 H St.; Washington, DC; 10-3
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 11; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 16)
      Residence; 1327 16th St.; Washington, DC; 10-4
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 24; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 17)
      Residences; 1711-13 St.; Washington, DC; 10-5; Mrs. Pendletter
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 18)
      Residence; 1765 Q ST.; Washington, DC; 10-6
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 19)
      Residence of Geo. Fraser; 20th cor. R St.; Washington, DC; 10-7; Newspaper
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 20)
      Residence; Conn. Ave. cor. 20th; Washington, DC; 10-8
    - "Private Houses", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 21)
      Residence; 1505 12th St. NW; Washington, DC; 10-9
    - "Private Houses", 1894 March 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 22)
      "Suburban Homes"; O St. bet. 21st and 22nd; Washington, DC; 10-10
    - Rock Creek Church, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 23)
      No. 15 (Fragile--plate is cracked)
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 24)
      Piney Branch; above the bridge at mouth; Washington, DC; Box 12, No. 1
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1894 June 4; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 25)
      Rock Creek; near Military Road; Washington, DC; No. 1; Box 12, No. 2
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1894 June 4; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 26)
      Rock Creek; near Military Road; Washington, DC; No. 2; Box 12, No. 3
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1894 June 4; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 27)
      Rock Creek; near Military Road; Washington, DC; No. 3; Box 12, No. 4
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 28)
      Mouth of Rock Creek; Washington, DC; Box 12; No. 5
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 29)
      Canal boats in Rock Creek; Washington, DC; Box 12, No. 6
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", 1895 March 10; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 11, Item 30)
      Rock Creek from Klingle Run Bridge; Washington, DC; Box 12, No. 8
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 1)
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 2)
      Rock Creek in Zoo Park
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 3)
      Rock Creek, DC
    - "Rock Creek Scenery", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 4)
    - Rock Creek, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 5)
      Adams Memorial; Monument, Rock Creek Park Cemetery
    - Rock Creek, 1898 August 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 6)
      Piney Branch Bridge; Seed 27 G.E. 12N; taken August 18th 1898; 1 sec; # 3 stops; No. 6
    - Rock Creek, 1898 August 24; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 7)
      Seed Nou. Sd. 27. 10.30; taken August 24th 1898; 1 sec; #3 stops; No. 7
    - Rock Creek, 1898 August 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 8)
      View in Rock Creek Park; Seed 27 G.E.; taken Aug 18th 1898; 1 sec; #3 stop; No. 8
    - Smithsonian Castle, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 9)
    - Soldier's Home, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 10)
      Main building
    - State, War, and Navy Building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 5)
    - State, War & Navy Department, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 11)
    - Statue, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 5)
      Andrew Jackson
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 6)
      McPherson Statue; Washington, DC. (plate is cracked)
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 7)
      Washington Statue.
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 8)
      Scott Statue; Washington, DC; Weight 12,000 lbs.
    - "Statues", 1894 Feburary 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 9)
      Jackson Statue showing White House, etc.; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 10)
      Jackson Statue; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 11)
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 12)
      Lafayette Statue; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1894 August 19; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 8)
      Lincoln's Emancipation Statue
    - "Statues", 1893 December; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 13)
      Thomas Statue; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1894 March 4; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 14)
      Capitol, and Garfield Statue; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1894 August 19; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 15)
      Garfield Statue.
    - "Statues", 1894 March 18; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 16)
      Statue of Martin Luther; Washington, DC.
    - "Statues", 1885 November 29; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 17)
      Farrugut Statue; Washington, DC.; Plate is missing 3 corners
    - "Statues", 1895 March 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 9)
      Greene's Statue; Stanton, Sq.; Washington, DC
    - "Statues", 1894 August 19; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 7)
      Peace Monument
    - "Statues", 1895 November 30; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Broken Glass plate negative--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 6)
      Admiral Dupont Statue
    - "Statues", Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 10)
    - Treasury Department, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 18)
      West Front
    - Van Ness Mansion, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 19)
      17th St. between B. and C. Sts. NW; Washington, DC; "This building stood on the site now occupid by the Bureau of American Republics."
    - Washington, District of Columbia, Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 20)
    - Washington Monument, 1894 November 29; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 21)
      From Agricultural Dep't grounds.
    - Washington Monument, 1895 March 22; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 22)
      From Bureau of Engraving.
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 23)
    - Washington Monument, 1898 December 14; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 24)
      No. 2; Clear day; 2.45 pm; Beck lens; 16 stop; 1 sec exposure; Seed's Plate, Gilt Edge 27.
    - Washington Monument, 1898 December 14; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 25)
      No. 3; Clear day; 3 pm; Beck lens; 64 stop; 3 sec exposure; Seed's Gilt Edge 27. Plates.
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 26)
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 12)
      "Monument"
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 13)
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 14)
    - Washington Monument, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 15)
    - White House, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 16)
    - White House, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 17)
    - Unidentified Location, Virginia, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 27)
      "Duck Yard"; No. 34; At a particular VA farmyard
    - Unidentified Location, Washington, DC, 1895 August 24; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 28)
      Cows in Pasture
    - Unidentified Location, Washington, DC, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 29)
      Residences
    - Unidentified Location, Washington, DC, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 12, Item 30)
    - Unidentified Location, Washington, DC, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 3 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 18)
      Possibly Treasury Department
  - Unidentified locations, Series 1 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains glass plate negatives of locations Hubbard did not identify. The material in this subseries is undated. As a whole, this subseries focuses on topographical images of landscapes, beach scenes, boating scenes, street scenes, and domestic scenes.
    - Unidentified Location, Aerial view of city, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Location, American Flag, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 3)
      Man posing with plant
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 4)
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Location, Amorphophallus Plant, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 8)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 9)
      Child posing on beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 10)
      Crowd at beach with pier in the background
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 11)
      Crowd at beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 13)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 14)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 15)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 16)
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 17)
      Five people on the beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 18)
      Four women in matching outfits posing on the beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 19)
      Girl and child posing on the beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 20)
      Man posing at beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 21)
      Nine people sitting on the beach together
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 22)
      Thirteen people posing on the beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 23)
      Two women laughing on the beach
    - Unidentified Location, Beach Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 24)
      Women posing at beach
    - Unidentified Location, Bird Coop, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 25)
    - Unidentified Location, Bird Coop, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 26)
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 27)
      The "Alma Evans" also the "Admiral"; No. 52
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 28)
      Boat on River
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 29)
      Boat on Water
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 13, Item 30)
      Boy rescued from drowning; at Ritter's; No. 106
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 1)
      Brigantine "Bruce Hawkins" Cranfords; No. 63
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 2)
      "Daisy" under full sail; No. 58
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 3)
      Daisy off the Cranfords Paving Co.; No. 61
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 4)
      Docked boat
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 5)
      "Ellie W."; Chas. Linkins Naptha Launch; No. 90; Velox 1 m. 35 s.
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 6)
      "Ellie W."; Chas. Linkins Naptha Launch, at a standstill; No. 91; Velox 1 m. 20 s.
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 7)
      Ferry "Belle Haven"; No. 59
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 8)
      Halcyon; No. 103
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 9)
      Halcyon; taken by Cliff Smith; No. 135
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 10)
      Halcyon; taken by Cliff Smith; No. 136
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 11)
      Halcyon; taken by J.E.L.; No. 137
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 12)
      Jennie Lippit; No. 8
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 13)
      Jennie Lippit; No. 9
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 14)
      Large boat with passengers on deck
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 15)
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 16)
      One canoe and two other boats with two men
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 17)
      One canoe and two other boats
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 18)
      Sailboat in the distance
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 19)
      Sailboat on water; lighthouse in the background
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 20)
      Sailboat on water with other boat in foreground
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 21)
      Sailboats on water
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 22)
      Sailboat on water
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 23)
      Sailboat with two passengers
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 24)
      Steamer "Samuel J. Pentz"; No. 60
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 25)
      Two boats with additional boats in the distance
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 26)
      Two men on a boat
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 27)
      Two sailboats with passengers
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 28)
      Two sailboats
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 29)
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 14, Item 30)
    - Unidentified Location, Boat and Cruising Scene, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 1)
      Winter aspect along the riverfront; No. 131
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 2)
      Large stone bridge and pedestrian bridge
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 3)
      Reflection of stone bridge in water
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 4)
      Wooden bridge
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Location, Bridge, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 22, Item 19)
    - Unidentified Location, Buildings on Shoreline, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 8)
    - Unidentified Location, Buildings on Shoreline, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 9)
    - Unidentified Location, Building on Shoreline, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 10)
    - Unidentified Location, Building on Shoreline, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 11)
    - Unidentified Location, Building on Shoreline, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Location, Building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 4, Box 22, Item 20)
      Building with Cannons in foreground
    - Unidentified Location, Building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 13)
      May be Boston related; likely Faneuil Hall
    - Unidentified Location, Building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 14)
      Small brick building (pump house?)
    - Unidentified Location, Building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 15)
    - Unidentified Location, Campsite, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 16)
    - Unidentified Location, Campsite, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 17)
    - Unidentified Location, Campsite, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 18)
    - Unidentified Location, Campsite, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 19)
    - Unidentified Location, Canal Lock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 20)
    - Unidentified Location, Canal Lock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 21)
    - Unidentified Location, Canal Lock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 22)
    - Unidentified Location, Carriages and Coaches, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 23)
      Hackney Lauden; No. 153